{
  "totalQuestions": 10,
  "questions": [
    {
      "id": "1",
      "question": "What should you be doing as soon as possible?",
      "answers": ["Going to Jail", "Completing a Property Set", "Making Trades", "Obtain all Four Railroads"],
      "correctAnswer": "Completing a Property Set"
    },
    {
      "id": "2",
      "question": "Which of these colors is it most likely to land on?",
      "answers": ["Green", "Brown", "Teal", "Orange"],
      "correctAnswer": "Orange"
    },
    {
      "id": "3",
      "question": "With all of the properties claimed with houses or hotels built on them, and you are in jail. It is safer to get out of jail as quickly as you can.",
      "answers": ["True", "False"],
      "correctAnswer": "False"
    },
    {
      "id": "4",
      "question": "How many houses should you build on a property as soon as possible?",
      "answers": ["3", "4", "2", "1"],
      "correctAnswer": "3"
    },
    {
      "id": "5",
      "question": "Hotels and Utilities are not efficient.",
      "answers": ["True", "False"],
      "correctAnswer": "False"
    },
    {
      "id": "6",
      "question": "All properties are taken and your opponent is in jail. What should you do after you move for your turn?",
      "answers": ["Build mores houses or upgrade to a Hotel", "Save money in case you land on a opposing tile", "Trade your property for better ones", "Stop playing the game because you have already won"],
      "correctAnswer": "Save money in case you land on a opposing tile"
    },
    {
      "id": "7",
      "question": "A property owner must ask for rent, if they donâ€™t, you are not required to pay.",
      "answers": ["True", "False"],
      "correctAnswer": "True"
    },
    {
      "id": "8",
      "question": "What is the maximum number of available houses in a game?",
      "answers": ["34", "30", "32","None of the above"],
      "correctAnswer": "32"
    },
    {
      "id": "9",
      "question": "Which of these colors is it most likely to land on?",
      "answers": ["Blue", "Magenta", "Orange", "Red"],
      "correctAnswer": "Orange"
    },
    {
      "id": "10",
      "question": "Which of the following two colors are they more likely to land on?",
      "answers": ["Red and Magenta", "Red and Orange", "Blue and Orange", "Orange and Green"],
      "correctAnswer": "Red and Orange"
    }
  ]
}
